MINGYU.ZHAO

Liaoning Shenyang No. 97 Wanghua mid Street

Mobile: +8615940217631

Email: mingyu.zhao.sjtu@gmail.com Home Page: www.mingyuzhao.net/blog

MYSELF

Three years' working experience and four years' R&D experiences.

Major interest is in all kinds of internet related technologies and designing and innovating various websites.

Two years' working experience in the field of information security.

Familiar with JAVA and owning experience in designing and researching J2EE.

Having written some little projects via PHP and Python.

Indicted to Windows, but also writing programs in the environment of Linux.

Rich experience in R&D model of Scrum and even hanging a whiteboard designed in Scrum at home.

Aggressive and work-alcoholic, not feeling comfortable if the daily meeting was not held.

EDUCATION

2006-2010 B.A., School of software, Shanghai Jiao Tong University

Majors

· Overview of software engineering, Software process, Software project management infrastructure, Algorithms and data structures, Databases, Enterprise information systems theory, Information systems design and implementation

WORKING EXPERIENCE

2012.7 – 2013.8 Manager, Liaoning Yuantong Logistics Co., Ltd.

· Investigate and design a logistics systems for the company, with the help of another software company.

2011.7 - 2012.7 Software Engineer , Ericsson Shanghai R&D center Team SimFAST

- · Simulate test server which is used to replace the real servers for our function tester. By doing this, the company could save millions of dollars per year.
- · Using Test Driven Develop (TDD) as the default development method.

2011.7 - 2012.7 Software Engineer , *Ericsson Shanghai R&D center Team Design and Maintenance*

· Maintain SGSN (The core server in communication network), handle trouble reports from our customers all over the world and give the quick and accurate response.

2011.7 - 2012.7 Internship, Microsoft Shanghai R&D center

· Use the latest AMT technology provided by Intel and other information/technology provided by Microsoft, to build up a remote computer control system including power up and shutting down.

SKILLS

Program JAVA, C#, TTCN3, Erlang, Python, PHP

Framework Yii for PHP, SSH for J2EE , .NET framework

Database MySQL , SQL Server

Foreign English

Language